I got basically no sleep last night!
Good morning.
Really?
G-Good morning, Senpai!
Morning.
Oh, Fudo.
Here, it's addressed to you.
You can tell, right? I've got
major bags under my eyes.
I can see them!
It's so important to get
proper sleep at night.
Senpai?
What's up? You look like you've seen a ghost.
N-N-Nothing!
I know everything
Desumi-san, we've got a problem.
Episode 8     Everybody Has a Secret or Two
You're so awesome, Desumi.
You always make your own lunches?
It's not so hard once you get used to it.
Really?
Sorry, Desucchi. Mouth slipped.
Are you all right, Desumi?
Rattled...
W-Well... I'm pretty used to it by now...
That makes it even worse!
Terror
What? You got a problem?
No...
You bet we got a problem.
You're always pickin' on Reaper—
on Desumi Magahara.
Sounds like someone needs a little
help learning right from wrong.
Student council president!
Discipline officer!
Beast Princess, A.K.A.
Kiki Majima
Steel Princess, A.K.A.
Kyoko Kuroyuri
Reaper Princess, A.K.A.
Desumi Magahara
Allow me to explain!
On Gekko's orders,
the Princess Series,
including Reaper Princess,
all attend the same school!
And why don't you ever stand up for yourself?
Give as good as you get once in a while.
Well, it's just a rice ball. No big deal.
Really? It's not?
Knock it off! You're gonna
make everything worse!
Well, anyway...
Hojo of Class 2-B.
Your skirt length, nails, earrings,
and just about everything else
are in violation of school rules!
Come to the guidance office later!
Meh, sounds dumb.
You guys must be starved
for romantic attention.
Am not!
No attention
When it comes to rice
balls or anything else...
I get what I want, no matter what it takes.
And right now, what I want most is...
What do you think?
Well...
It's a secret.
You don't get to know, Desucchi.
What's her problem?
What kind of loser keeps secrets, anyway?
Now, now. Everybody has a secret or two.
What?!
It's that happy-go-lucky attitude
that makes you a target, y'know!
If you don't want me to make this picture public,
come to Central Park tomorrow at 8 PM
Hey!
You really came, huh? Hilarious.
A-Are you the one who sent me this?
Correct.
I'm the one who took that picture.
Red Gelato... Fudo Aikawa.
Why in the world are you doing this?
Who exactly are you?
You really think I'm gonna give up my name?
You've probably guessed by now, but I can
send out that picture anytime I want.
That'd be a problem for you, right?
Yes, it would be.
So you're just gonna have
to do whatever I say.
Whether you play along or not will decide
if the picture stays private or—
P-Please!
Uh?
Promise that when you publish the picture,
you'll put a censorship bar over her eyes!
What?
I'm begging you!
That's the problem?
You're okay with it going public otherwise?
Absolutely!
That doesn't make sense.
Your reputation—
I don't care about my reputation!
But... I really don't want
to make any trouble for her.
And...
If the picture were to go out uncensored,
she would quickly go viral
as an angel on earth!
Plus, agents would be falling all
over themselves to recruit her!
Idol! Model! Actress!
She'll get all kinds of offers,
and before I know it, she'll have
ascended far beyond my reach!
It's too terrifying to conceive!
You're a creepy little man.
Well, fine.
One way or another, you don't
want me leaking it, right?
Which means you've gotta
do whatever I tell you.
Got it?
Y-Yes...
Then you'd better break up with her—
I will not!
Hey!
Squeeze
Since when do you get a
choice in the whole thing?!
Don't you get what's going on here?
B-But I'd really appreciate
it if you wouldn't go there!
Would you accept an alternative?
Alternative?
Well...
Okay.
Record
Recording
Then, tell me you love me!
I will not!
Have a little tact, jerk!
Fine. I'm gonna call the tabloids.
Wait!
What exactly are you after here?
Are you trying to come between us?
Oh, shut up.
Listen up... here's your last chance.
K-Kiss my hand!
I'll get a picture of you groveling,
and make our master-slave relationship clear.
Is this the kind of thing
you called me out for?
Just do it already!
Master-slave relationship?
I...
I can't do it!
It's freaking humiliating!
Huh?
Fine, I'll let you off with a warning!
But tomorrow, I'm gonna think of way
more disgusting things for you to do!
You'd better be ready!
And if you don't come,
that picture goes everywhere!
You big, stupid jerk!
Huh?
And that's what happened, Desumi-san.
Who in the world is she?
Well, she didn't give her name,
so I don't know who she is...
But I'm set to meet her again tonight.
I'll just have to silence her permanently.
Please don't go right to those thoughts!
What exactly did she try to get you to do?
Oh, well...
She wanted me to kiss her hand—
But I didn't!
Y-You really didn't?
I didn't.
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
A-Anything else?
She wanted me to say I love her.
She even asked me to break up with you.
I haven't the foggiest
idea what she's thinking.
Desumi-san?
Fudo...
I think she's...
in love.
In love? With whom?
You're not saying...
She's in love with me?!
It's all right, Desumi-san.
There's nothing to worry about.
I feel bad for the girl,
but I need to make things clear to her.
Good boy. You actually came!
I'm sorry, girl whose name I don't know!
I thought it over, and realized how you feel.
I truly appreciate the
feelings you have for me.
What?
I acted truly shameful yesterday.
Wait—
But I cannot return your feelings—
Stop—
S...
Stop!
What in the world are you talking about?!
But you're in love, aren't you?
What?!
With me?
Heck no! I'm in love with Desucchi!
Crap! I said it out loud!
Wow, she's so tacky.
Bet she's easy.
She's kinda scary.
She'd blow her top over nothing.
Better stay away.
Oh, wow! I love your nails!
Oh, sorry to ambush you.
But I always want to do mine that way,
and it never turns out right!
Oh... yeah?
I'm Desumi Magahara.
Nice to meet you!
Desucchi was so honest and innocent.
I've had a huge crush on her ever since.
No reaction, huh?
Sorry to besmirch your pure little
Desucchi with my unworthy feelings!
Nothing to be sorry for!
I was just thinking, you have
incredibly good taste!
I'm so glad to meet someone else
who sees how amazing she is!
I know!
Want to stay up all night and
talk about how great she is?!
Well?
You're so weird.
Talking sounds fun, but I'll pass for now.
We're still kinda like rivals, you know?
Hey, Red Gelato...
No, Fudocchi.
"Fudocchi"?
Sorry about all the trouble I made.
I'm probably gonna keep
making trouble, just FYI.
R-Right...
I'm kind of self-centered,
I'm a little perverse...
And...
I just never know when to quit.
Besides, Desucchi and
I have a secret connection.
My own little secret that
even Desucchi doesn't know.
Better keep your guard up,
or I'll steal her from you!
See ya!
A secret?
A meeting this early in
the morning? I've got the worst luck.
The early bird gets the worm, Beast-san.
Don't lecture me when I'm the
one who had to wake you up.
Sheesh...
Hey, Heat.
What's up with her? Learn some
basic manners already.
Don't say that, Beast.
No one's ever seen her face or
heard her real voice, right?
I don't trust her.
I think it's just fine.
Everybody has a secret or two.
Oh? Does that mean you're
hiding something, Reaper?
What? O-Of course not!
My own little secret that
even Desucchi doesn't know.
Desucchi is as adorable as ever!
Gekko Princess Series
Heat Princess
Anna Hojo
Love After World Domination!
I'm so nervous!
It's all right, Desumi-san.
Believe in us!
Your compatibility rating is 98%!
Isn't that great, Fudo—
Why do you look so unhappy?
It wasn't 100%...
You're so hard on yourself.
Excuse me, could I drop in?
What is it, Haru?
Desumi-san.
Does Gekko have any attack plans tomorrow?
This is off the record, okay?
Bosslar-sama won't be in tomorrow,
so all attacks are off!
Awesome!
So, Fudo-senpai,
can you help me study tomorrow?
Finals are coming up,
and I haven't done any test prep!
Sure, that's fine.
Wait, Fudo, are you a really good student?
Despite how he looks, Senpai is
always in the top ten for his year!
Despite how he looks!
That's awesome!
How exactly do I look?
How exactly
do I look?
Very well!
We'll have a study hangout tomorrow.
Thank you!
Are you bad at school too, Desumi-san?
Y-Yes...
Then let's make it a threesome!
But if we do that, we won't
be able to do it at HQ...
Let's do it at my place, then!
What?
Gekko
The
Next
Day
Desumi-san... is this...
The Gekko women's dormitory!
That's what I thought!
Come on, this is way too dangerous!
Right, Senpai?
Walking on air
Desumi-san's room. Desumi-san's room.
Desumi-san's room. Desumi-san's room...
Never mind. He's already walking on air.
Don't worry, Haru.
Just put this on, and you'll be fine!
You really think it'll be that easy?
You have it on backwards!
I'm so scared...
What's the password?
Briar rose!
You may pass!
Kii!
K-Kii!
Okay, we're here!
Shouldn't your security be
a little tighter than this?
Desumi-san, your room is so cute!
At last...
At last, I have reached the promised land!
The holy ground I previously
only saw in video calls!
It smells like Desumi-san!
Never mind the studying, let's—
Sorry, I lost control there.
Let's begin studying.
Fudo-sensei, thank you for the lesson!
Thank you both for coming!
Math II
Year 2  Term 2  Midterm  Answer Sheet
2-A Desumi Magahara
All perfect scores!
Hang on! You're awesome at school!
What's going on here, Desumi-san?
Did you just want to study with us?
Y-Yes...
Oh so cute!
Oh so cute
So I'm the only hopeless one here?
As charming as this is, rules are rules.
Very well. Go on and do it!
Thwap.
Thwap
I got a strike for lying.
So cute!
I'm sorry for lying to you about
being bad at school, Haru.
Shame...
I'm actually very good at school!
That apology wasn't great.
Then let's try again!
We'll both teach you!
Yeah! I'm gonna learn so much!
That's not the way, now.
That's not going to get you to the answer.
Imagine that the value of
X is the bicep brachii.
What does that make Y?
I don't know.
The forearm flexors, of course!
Now solve the next problem,
supposing that X is your deltoid.
I can't solve it—
Bear in mind its connection
to the pectoralis major!
If you can't sort it out, drawing out
the anatomy might help.
Drawing the anatomy?!
Yes! That should do it!
Crap!
I read so much BL, I actually did it!
The connection between math
and muscles is inseparable.
Everything makes more sense when you liken
the beauty of solving equations
to well-strengthened muscles.
Help me, Desumi-san!
Just as muscles connect in a
beautiful way, the numbers—
Hey, come on. You're just confusing her.
Let me teach her.
Don't overthink it!
All you need for math problems is spirit!
Just fill in that formula, wham!
Which formula, exactly?
You know, the wobbly one!
With the smooth lines in it.
Then give it a wha-chock and the
answer will come out like yeah!
Ah.
Liken it to the parallel curves
of the trapezius and the deltoids!
They're awful teachers.
Just wham those numbers
down in front of you,
Understanding muscles will deepen
your understanding of math!
and don't be afraid to smack that
formula in there right after!
Timing is important there.
Similarly, understanding muscles
means understanding math!
Sometimes they get you on your heels,
There's nothing else to it!
but just make sure to stay flexible
and they'll tap out eventually,
Additionally, likening unequal equations
to the biceps femoris is quite famous—
Um...
so pay close attention to—
I should probably go.
You've got it down already?
Haru's such a quick learner!
We must be great teachers!
I really envy you two.
You'll have your choice of university.
University?
I've gotta work hard to
get into my first choice!
Hmph
Happy to help anytime. Just ask.
Thanks for everything.
I'll be going now.
Sure thing. See you again!
Alone with Desumi-san in her room...
I suddenly feel so nervous.
What's wrong?
You look strangely serious.
Sorry.
I was just thinking about what Haru said.
Fudo, are you moving on to
university after high school?
Yes.
I want to study education.
And someday, I want to become an elementary
school teacher and teach children.
I want to be a hero-slash-teacher.
Desumi-san, do you have
a goal for the future?
I...
I want to go to the same university you do.
I want a front-row seat to you
making your dream come true.
That's a goal I just came up with.
Desumi-san...
But I think my father would
probably be really against it.
I think he expects me to go full-time
with Gekko after I graduate high school.
Hey, if it comes to that,
I'll convince your father!
I can always count on you!
I hope we can go together, Fudo.
I know we will.
Even someone like me can become a hero.
There's no goal that can't be reached.
Yeah.
Oh, I bet that's Haru.
Maybe she forgot something!
Desumi-sensei!
It's your daddy!
Came to see ya in person for once!
I brought torimon, too!
This is... not good.
Open up already!
Desumi-san!
Hey.
Are you listening?
Desumi-san!
Shut up!
Next episode is, "My Big Sister Has Changed."
Episode 9    My Big Sister Has Changed
Get it now?
Yes.